Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Fishes and Fishing, PhC.42.Fish; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Crappie, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (6n), PhC.42.Bx11.Fish.F6-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Tuna, Drum Inlet, 1941. (3), PhC.42.Bx11.Fish.F7-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Tuna, Drum Inlet, 1941. (3), PhC.42.Bx11.Fish.F7-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mounted Large mouth Black Bass., PhC.42.Bx11.Fish.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Diagram of Escolars, from Field Book of Marine Fishes, 1938., PhC.42.Bx11.Fish.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Duncan Oyster Factory, Beaufort, NC, ca. 1900. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F41-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Duncan Oyster Factory, Beaufort, NC, ca. 1900. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F41-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Seine Shad, Avoca, NC, 1884. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Seining Shad, Avoca, NC, 1884. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F43-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Seining Shad, Avoca, NC, 1884. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F43-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster Cannery, ca. 1880s., PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F44; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Purse seining for menhaden, Beaufort, NC, 1884 (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F45-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Purse seining for menhaden, Beaufort, NC, 1884 (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F45-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unloading shad or menhaden, ca. 1880s. (N.83.6.182), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F46; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hauling seine, ca. 1880s, PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Folder Dock scene showing commercial fishing, ca. 1880s. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F48-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Folder Dock scene showing commercial fishing, ca. 1880s. (2), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F48-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mullet seining, Brunswick Co. or Beaufort, NC, 1884., PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F49; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mullet seining, Brunswick Co. or Beaufort, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Menhaden Scrap and Oil Factory, Beaufort, NC, ca. 1880s. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F51; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Menhaden Scrap and Oil Factory, Beaufort, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F52; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish House, Edenton, NC, 1884. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F53; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hanging Gill Nets, ca. 1880s., PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F54; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hauling for fish, Beaufort, NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F55; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Beaching the haul of seine, Pamlico Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx12.Fish.F56; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Hatcheries, PhC.42.Hatcheries; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old State Fish Hatchery, Raleigh, NC, 1880s, PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old State Fish Hatchery, Raleigh, NC, 1880s, PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - State Carp Ponds, Raleigh, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - State Carp Ponds, Raleigh, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - State Carp Ponds, Raleigh, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - State Carp Ponds, Raleigh, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - State Carp Ponds, Raleigh, NC, 1884. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.Hatcheries.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Fisheries, PhC.42.Fisheries; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish Scrap and Oil Factory, Beaufort, NC, 1880., PhC.42.Bx12.Fisheries.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Purse seining for menhaden, Beaufort, NC, 1880s., PhC.42.Bx12.Fisheries.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad and Herring Fishery, Chowan River, Bertie Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx12.Fisheries.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Long Hauling, Avoca, Chowan River, ca. 1903., PhC.42.Bx12.Fisheries.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steam flat and Great Seine Fishery, Chowan River, Bertie Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx12.Fisheries.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Fishing Camps, PhC.42.FishCamps; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, Topsail, Pender Co., NC, ca. 1928. (3n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F10-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, Topsail, Pender Co., NC, ca. 1928. (3n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F10-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, Topsail, Pender Co., NC, ca. 1928. (3n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F10-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1900-1903, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1918. (3n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F11-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1918. (3n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F11-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Capt. George Rollingson, Fish House, Elizabeth City, NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1900-1903, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish Trap, near Edenton, NC, ca. 1904. (1), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish Trap, near Edenton, NC, ca. 1904. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Catch, Barn Slue Camp, Dare Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Catch, Barn Slue Camp, Dare Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish Camp Crew, Baum Slue, Oregon Inlet, ca. 1903., PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F3-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F3-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shad Fishery Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC 1905, PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish catch, Barn Slue Fishing Camp, ca. 1908. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917., PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, Topsail Island, Pender Co., NC, ca. 1928. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Camp, Topsail Island, Pender Co., NC, ca. 1928. (n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Barn Slue Fishing Camp, Dare Co., NC, ca. 1905.(n), PhC.42.Bx12.FishCamps.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Plants, PhC.42.Plants; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Yellow Lady Slipper Transparency, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Yellow Lady Slipper Transparency, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Yellow Lady Slipper Transparency, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Yellow Lady Slipper Transparency, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Skunk Cabbage Feb 1976, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Skunk Cabbage Feb 1976, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F1-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pitcher Plant, American Holly, Turk's Cap Lily. (3 PCD), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pitcher Plant, American Holly, Turk's Cap Lily. (3 PCD), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pitcher Plant, American Holly, Turk's Cap Lily. (3 PCD), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sand Vetch, Washington, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Large Fungus. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Egyptian Lotus, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1908. (2n), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Egyptian Lotus, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1908. (2n), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chrysanthemums, ca. 1910. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Castor Bean Plant, 16 feet, Fayetteville, NC, 1915, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F7-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Daisies, n.d. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F7-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Daisies, n.d. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F7-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Natural Fernery, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F7-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hydrangea, Raleigh, NC, ca. 1910, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F8-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lotus Blossoms, Carp Ponds, ca. 1903, PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F8-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Rhododendron in bloom, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx13.Plants.F8-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Food, PhC.42.Food; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grocery Store Scenes, n.d. (5n), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grocery Store Scenes, n.d. (5n), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grocery Store Scenes, n.d. (5n), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grocery Store Scenes, n.d. (5n), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grocery Store Scenes, n.d. (5n), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bowl of Oyster Stew, n.d. (LS), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Five baskets of beans., PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oysters on the half shell, New Bern, NC, ca. 1906. (cyan), PhC.42.Bx13.Food.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Forestry and Forest Industry, PhC.42.Forestry; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Early Saw Mill, Moore Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain forest and rocky stream bed., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hoop and barrel factory, Western N.C., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Large Poplar tree., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Logging, Eastern N.C., ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - A country saw mill and grist mill., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Interior of a saw mill., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Vanderbilt's Lumbering Camp, Transylvania Co., NC. (N.76.8.318), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lumbering in a cypress swamp, Robeson Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dam to flush out logs. (N.76.8.320), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Forest scene, Wake Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Waste from factory cutting chair stock, near Julian, Guilford Co., NC. (LS), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified trees at Ocracoke, NC. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Live Oak, Orton Plantation, 1920, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F21-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lockwood Folly, 1939. (3n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F21-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lockwood Folly, 1939. (3n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F21-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Buxton Woods near Hatteras, NC, 1906., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Second growth Hardwoods., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fire-scarred, large tree., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Second growth Sycamore., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Logs Loading Car, Vanderbilt Estate, Biltmore, NC., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Forest Scene, ca. 1905. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Forest, Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1905. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Virgin Forest in the mountains, ca. 1905. (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Scraping" long leaf pine. (LS), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut Bark Disease, Greensboro, NC, 1913. (14), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F30-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Planting seedlings, Raleigh Boy Scouts, Lake Johnson, 1932. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F31-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Planting seedlings, Raleigh Boy Scouts, Lake Johnson, 1932. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F31-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two pines from the same stump, French's Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (6), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F32-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Locust and pine trees planted by the Raleigh Boy Scouts, Lake Johnson, 1931. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F33-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Locust and pine trees planted by the Raleigh Boy Scouts, Lake Johnson, 1931. (2), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F33-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Weeding nursery stock of forest trees, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F34-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hemlock in Nursery Stand, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F34-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Thickets of Stump sprouts Appearing Years After a Fire, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F34-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Young Timber, Recently Severely Injured by Fire, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F34-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Rocky Land Sustaining God forest Growth Yancey County, 1903-1904, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F34-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Young Loblolly Pines, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F35-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Thicket of Balm of Gilead Grown for Herbs, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F35-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pure second Growth of Short leaf pine, 40 years old, showing a good crown density on fair soil, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F35-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hardwood Forest, Density of Forest Under Harsh Condition of Growth, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F35-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Group of Huckleberry or Sycamore on Abandoned farmland near Haw River, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F35-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dense Growth of poles, 10 to 15 years old in abandoned swampland, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F36-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Blazes on a pine tree, gradually growing over and becoming obliterated, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F36-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Young Hardwood Growth; best condition after lumbering, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F36-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Influence of Lumbering on the second growth; Removal of swamp pine ahs given light for development of sour gum seedlings which arise from the great pack of the second growth, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F37-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Young pine thicket on abandoned pasture, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F37-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Second growth poles, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F37-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Reproduction of Elm under favorable conditions, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F38-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Reproduction of southern maple and red cedar on shady spot on woodside, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F38-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Reproduction of Southern Elm under favorable conditions, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F38-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - A good remnant of chestnut and oak forest, uninjured by fire, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F39-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hemlock forest, Nantahala Company, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F39-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut and Spanish Oak forest, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F39-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Saw Mill, Eastern N.C., ca. 1903-1904. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - good forest condition 10 years after moderate lumbering, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F40-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - 7 years before this picture was made (1947) this land was covered with hardwoods of little or no commercial value. Land was bulldozed and reseeded from natural sources. Now has thick stand of young pines, 12 to 15 feet high. Shown is Claiborne county, Fo, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F40-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - 2 year old southern pine plantation. EV Hogan, President, Norman Lumber Co, Norman, NC Stands in plantation of loblolly pines planted two years ago, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F40-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Close- Up of International Paper co sign shown and described in photo no cs-54-73(a), PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F41-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Signs on part of 8800 acre forest fire. Picture shows part of burn on lands of international Paper Co, between Conway and Myrtle Beach, SC, Believed to have been started by cigarette flipped from car window, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F41-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Eastern NC (Wake Co?) Green's Wood HHB 1900-1904?, PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain clearing, Macon Co., NC, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boundaries of Timber, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F44; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boundaries of Timber, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F45; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scenery, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F46; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - A fine hemlock forest, Mt. LeConte., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Second growth Hardwoods, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F48; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - River Birch, Macon Co., NC, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F49; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Saw Mill, no location given., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Hardwoods, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mill and Pine logs at a sawmill, no location given., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hardwood logs awaiting shipment., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Hardwood forest., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cypress forest of medium sized trees., PhC.42.Bx13.Forestry.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Balsam Christmas trees, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F51; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hardwood forest, Western, NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F52; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain valley hardwoods, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F53; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chestnut blight, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1909., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F54; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hardwood Timber, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F55; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Young Pine Timber, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F56; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Poor Forestry Management, Mitchell Co., NC, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F57; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Spruce Thickets, Mitchell Co., NC, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F58; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Forest, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F59; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fir trees, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F60; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified forests, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F61; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified forests, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F62; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified forests, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F63; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lumbering in Cypress Swamp, Robeson Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F64; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Forest condition on the Blue Ridge, ca. 1904., PhC.42.Bx14.Forestry.F65; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946